AFSCME, District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II: Executive Office Records, 1951-1999.
  - Subseries II:B: Lillian Roberts Associate Director Records, 1951-1983.
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Dietary Aide Training Program, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): History, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Mortuary Caretakers, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Roosevelt Island Parking, 1973-1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Uniform Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Local 768 (Health Services Employees), 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Local 957 (New York City Housing Authority Clericals), 1975-1979 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Local 1070 (Court, County and Department of Probation Employees), 1973-1977 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Local 1219 (Real Estate Employees): Housing Relocation Aides, 1971, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Local 1321 (Queens Library Guild), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Local 1359 (Rent Regulation Services Employees), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Local 1457 (Juvenile Center): Counselors, 1970, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees), 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Fort Greene Community Corporation, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Hunts Point Community Corporation, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Lower West Side Community Corporation, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Qualicap's Health and Welfare Action Center, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): South Bronx Community Corporation, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): South Brooklyn and Red Hook Community Corporations, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Southeast Queens Community Corporation, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Local 1503 (Metropolitan Museum of Art), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Local 1509 (Youth Board Employees), 1972-1980 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees), undated, 1978-1981 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Police Department, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees), 1972-1980 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Local 1931 (TBTA Maintenance Employees), 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Local 2021 (Off-Track Betting Corporation, OTB), Dec 1974-Mar 1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Local 2021 (OTB), Apr 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Local 2021 (OTB), 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Local 2507 (Ambulance Corpsmen), 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Local 2507 (Ambulance Corpsmen), 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Local 2507 (Ambulance Corpsmen), 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Local 2627 (New York City Electronic Data Processing Employees), 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - March on Washington (labor coalition), 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Mayor's Midtown Citizens Committee, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Medical Surgical Technician Training Program, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Membership Gain/Loss Records and Dues Check-off Reports, 1969-1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Methadone Maintenance Treatment Program, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Metropolitan Hospital, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Minority Advisory Committee to Secretary of U. S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Mobilization for Youth: "Establishing a New Career, The Social Health Technician", 1970 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Mobilization for Youth: New Occupations Demonstration Project, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Mobilization for Youth: Social Health and Psychiatric Technician Training Program, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Morrisania City Hospital, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Municipal Credit Union, 1974-Jun 1977 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Municipal Credit Union, Jul 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Municipal Credit Union, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Municipal Credit Union: Advisory Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Municipal Employees Legal Service Fund (MELS), 1973-1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - National Association of Health Services Executives, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - National Child Labor Committee: Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - National Science Foundation Research Project: "Relations Among Work Organization, Job Satisfaction, and Productivity", 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - New York City: "A Plan for Improving the Effectiveness of Hospital Services…" I, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - New York City: "A Plan for Improving the Effectiveness of Hospital Services…" II, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - New York City: "Plan for Localized Government", 1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - New York City Agency for Child Development, 1971-1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - New York City Board of Education: Addiction Prevention Program Instructors (Local 372), 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - New York City Department of Hospitals, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1975-Jun 1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC, Jul 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1976-Mar 1976 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - New York City HHC, Apr 1976-May 1976 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - New York City HHC, Sep 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1977-May 1977 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1977-Oct 1977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC, Nov 1977-Dec 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1978-Apr 1978 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC, May 1978-Sep 1978 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC, Oct 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC, Feb 1979-Mar 1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC, Apr 1979 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC, May 1979 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1979-Jul 1979 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC, Aug 1979-Oct 1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC, Nov 1979-Dec 1979 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1980-Feb 1980 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC, Mar 1980-May 1980 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1980-Oct 1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC, Nov 1980-Dec 1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC: Ad Hoc Panel on Threatened Strike ("Patterson Panel" and Tri-Partite Task Force on Proposed Layoffs), 1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, 1968-Feb 1971 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Mar 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Contracts and Financial Records, Jul 1970-Feb 1972 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Contracts and Financial Records, Apr 1972-Apr 1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Crisis Budget Information, 1974-Apr 1975 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Crisis Budget Information, undated, May 1975-Sep 1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Employee List, ca.1972 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Publicity, 1972-1975 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC: Affirmative Action Plan, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC: Bellevue Hospital Labor/Management Productivity Committee Report, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - New York City HHC: Board of Directors (Budget crisis), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - New York City HHC: Bronx Hospitals (Budget crisis), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - New York City HHC: Brooklyn Hospitals (Budget crisis), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - New York City HHC: Brooklyn Regionalization Program, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - New York City HHC: Budget Crisis, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - New York City HHC: Budget Crisis, CHP Reports, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - New York City HHC: Clerical Division, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - New York City HHC: Clippings, 1970-1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC: Community Boards, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC: Education and Training, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC: Education and Training, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC: Education and Training, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC: Education Programs, 1972-1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC: Emergency Medical Service (EMS), 1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC: EMS, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC: EMS Manhattan Plan, 1978-1982 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC: Ethnic Census, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC: Financial Plan Data, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC: Functional Program and Space Utilization Study, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC: Gouverneur Hospital Closing, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC: Joint Labor-Management Productivity Committee, Aug 1976-Mar 1977 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC: Joint Labor-Management Productivity Committee, Apr 1977-Sep 1978 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - New York City HHC: Labor-Management Conferences, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - New York City HHC: Layoff Analysis, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - New York City HHC: Medicaid Reimbursements (New York State Office of Health Systems Management), 1978 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - New York City HHC: Patient Accounting Proposal, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - New York City HHC: Personnel and Layoffs, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - New York City HHC: Personnel Review Board Decisions, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - New York City HHC: Press Releases, 1970-1977 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Committee, Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA) I, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Committee, Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA) II, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Program, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Working Papers, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Working Papers, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC: Professional Division (Local 1407), 1970 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC: Rollbacks, 1967-1973 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC: Roosevelt Island Laundry Closing, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC: Taylor Law Application (1976 Strike), 1970, 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC: Training Coalition, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC: Training Program for Billing/Collecting, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC: Tripartite Task Force on Potential Additional Sources of Revenue and Decentralization, Jul 1976 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC: Basic Education Program, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - New York City Housing and Development Administration (HDA), undated, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - New York City HDA: Community Liaison Workers (Local 371), 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - New York City HDA: Support Service Contracts, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - New York City Human Resources Administration, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - New York City Juvenile Justice Agency, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - New York City Manual of Personnel Policies, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - New York City Medical School Proposal, Jun 1972-Oct 1973 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - New York City Medical School Proposal, Feb 1974-Jul 1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - New York City Office of Labor Relations, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - New York City Unemployed and Welfare Council, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - New York State Advisory Council on Substance Abuse, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - New York State Department of Civil Service: Title and Salary Plan I, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - New York State Department of Civil Service: Title and Salary Plan II, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - New York State Department of Mental Hygiene: Inventory of Inservice Training Courses, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - New York State Division of Substance Abuse Services, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - New York State Employment and Training Council, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - New York Urban Coalition, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - New York Urban Coalition: Health Manpower Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - North Brooklyn Hospital Training Project, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - North Brooklyn Hospital Training Project (Woodhull Hospital): Proposal to Train Community Residents for Professional Positions, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Nurse's Aide to Licensed Practical Nurse (LPN) Upgrading Program, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program, Jan 1969-May 1969 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program, Jun 1969-Dec 1969 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Instruction for Blood Pressure, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Instruction on Vocational Adjustment I, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Instruction on Vocational Adjustment II, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Printed Material and Publicity, 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Feb 1968-Jun 1968 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Jun 1968-Nov 1968 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Nov 1968-Apr 1969 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Apr 1969-Sep 1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Nurse's Aide to LPN Upgrading Program: Quarterly Progress Reports, Sep 1969-Dec 1969 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 153, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Outside Activities, 1967-1971 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Personal Services Unit, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Personnel Issues, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Personnel Issues, 1970-1972 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Personnel Issues, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Personnel Issues, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Personnel Issues, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Pipeline Correspondence, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Political Action: Governor's Race (Rockefeller/Goldberg), 1970 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Productivity in City Agencies, 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Professional and Cultural Division: Monthly Staff Reports (Lubin, Castiglione, McCabe, Trotter, Hill, Shaplo, Baron), 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Public Service Employment Conference, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Queens General Hospital, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Reich, Chaim B., M.D., 1978 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: Health Services Mobility Study (HSMS) Plan of Work, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 1, "Train Practical Nurses to Become Registered Nurses" (Draft), 1968 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 1, "Train Practical Nurses to Become Registered Nurses: A Survey of the PN Point of View", 1968 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, Vol. 1, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals" (Draft)", 1969 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, Vol. 2, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals" (Draft), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals, Volume 1", 1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Report No. 2, "Occupational Structure of New York City Municipal Hospitals, Volume 2", 1969 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Research Reports Nos. 4 and 5, "Suggestions for Job and Curriculum Ladders in Health Center Ambulatory Care", 1972 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Second Progress Report, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report No. 2, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report No. 4, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report No. 7, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report Nos. 8-9, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Technical Report Nos. 10-11, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Working Paper No. 2, "A Pre-Test Manual for Task Identification", 1968 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Working Paper No. 4, "A Pre-Test Manual for Task Identification (Re-Test)", 1969 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Research Foundation, CUNY: HSMS Working Paper No. 7, "A Re-Test Manual for Scaling Task Dimensions", 1970 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Roberts, Lillian, undated, 1971-1972, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Safety Issues, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Safety Training, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - School Decentralization, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - School Volunteer Program, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Schools Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Apr 1974-Jun 1974 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Schools Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Jul 1974-Feb 1975 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Schools Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Mar 1975-Jul 1976 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Seaview Hospital, undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Segundo Ruiz Belvis Neighborhood Family Care Center, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Society for Advanced Medical Systems (SAMS), 1978 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Speaking Engagements and Speeches, undated, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Speaking Engagements and Speeches, 1972-1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Speaking Engagements and Speeches: RAND Institute, Job Enrichment, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - State University of New York: Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Stationary Firemen, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Surgical Group Practice, Bellevue Hospital, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Sydenham Hospital, 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Sydenham Hospital, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Sydenham Hospital, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Television Series, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Trade Union Committee to Restore Welfare, Medicaid, and School Lunch Cuts I, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Trade Union Committee to Restore Welfare, Medicaid, and School Lunch Cuts II, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - United States Census, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare: State Health Careers Councils and Committees Workshop, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - White Collar Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Apr 1974-Sep 1974 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - White Collar Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Oct 1974-Feb 1975 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - White Collar Division: Monthly Staff Reports, Mar 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Wildcat Services Corporation (Vera Institute of Justice), 1973-1977 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Women's Political Training Center, Hunter College: Advisory Board, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Woodhull Hospital, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Woodhull Hospital: Mayor's Committee on Woodhull Report, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Work in America Institute: National Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Work Incentive Program (WIN) and New York Work Rules, ca.1970, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Work Relief Employment Program (WREP): Post-Certification, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Workmen's Compensation, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Series III: Legal Department Records, 1956-1986.
  - AFSCME Attorney's Conference, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, Community and Social Agency Employees Union (CSAE): Agreements, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1979-1981 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Agreements, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Constitution and Related Correspondence, undated, 1980-1984 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37 I, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37 II, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37 III, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME, DC 1707, CSAE: Proposed Merger with DC 37, Background Material, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Board of Education v. Vincent J. Byrne: Affidavits, 1975, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Background Materials, 1963-1976 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Court Papers, 1975-1977 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Exhibits, 1975-1977 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Memoranda and Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Notes, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts I, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts II, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts III, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts IV, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Board of Education v. Byrne: Transcripts (Partial), ca.1977 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Butler, James (Local 420) v. DC 37: Accounting, ca.1979 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, James Butler, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, Lester Wright, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, Lillian Roberts, 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavit, Victor Gotbaum, 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavits, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Affidavits, Local 420 Members, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Butler v. DC 37: Appellate Division Arguments, Notes, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 8)